http://www.pmsa.org.uk/privacy-policy

AwardsSculpture JournalDonate
Promoting | Protecting | Preserving our public monuments and sculpture
PMSA Privacy PolicyAbout this Privacy PolicyPMSA is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Please read this privacy policy carefully so that you can see why and how we collect data from you and how it will be used by us.For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 and any subsequent amendments, PMSA is the “data controller”. Our registered company address is: 70 Cowcross Street, London, EC1M 6EJ. If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or the personal information we have about you, please contact:Address: PMSA, 70 Cowcross Street, London, EC1M 6EJWhen do we collect your personal information? We would really like to send you details about our products, services, projects, events, offers and promotions but we will only do so when you tell us that you are happy to receive this information. You can let us know that you would like to receive this information online when you purchase tickets, enter competitions, buy merchandise or sign-up to our newsletter.We will also use your personal information when you buy subscriptions, publications, event tickets, products and services from us. This is only so that we can complete your order but we won’t use your personal information for marketing purposes unless you tell us this is ok.All the information you give to us is confidential. We will only use your information in the way we tell you in this policy.What personal information do you give us? You may provide us with your name, address, date of birth; payment address; delivery address; financial information including your credit, or debit card or other payment information you provide when filling in forms on our website; or when corresponding with us by phone or email; your purchase history of PMSA products and services; and any information you decide to share with us.What personal information do we give to third parties? Your privacy is important to us and so we will never sell or disclose your personal information to a third party for the use of the information for other purposes than described in this policy.We may give your personal information to our successors, assigns and trusted service partners for delivering services to you. For instance, for the purposes of fulfilling subscriptions, marketing, finance, advertising, processing payment, delivery and other in-store and out-store services.To prevent fraud or other criminal activity and to make sure your information is accurate, we may pass on the information we have about you to other companies, retailers, financial organisations or other organisations specialising in the prevention of fraud and crime. We are sometimes obligated to disclose the information we have about customers to law enforcement agencies where an allegation has been made of suspected criminal activity.  We may also purchase services and data from agencies to verify the contact details and personal information you have provided to us.We will make sure that your personal information is protected when it is sent outside of PMSA.  We make sure our successor, assigns and trusted service partners keep your personal information safe.What we do with the personal information you provide to us? We use the information you give to us in a number of different ways:Processing orders and deliveryTo process your order ensuring that the personal and financial information you provide is accurate. For this, we use payment systems of trusted third parties to ensure that your payment is safe and that your details are not being used fraudulently. We use systems of fraud analysis, which ensure that genuine and accurate payment details are being provided to PMSA for any purchase. We may also use credit agencies to perform this task for us.To ensure that the products and services you buy from us are delivered to the correct address. This involves working with trusted third parties who are based outside of PMSA and sharing with them the personal information you have provided. For example, your name, address for delivery and any delivery preferences you have outlined to us such as the time of day you wish to receive a delivery.We may store and process the information you provide for a period of time to ensure that any allegation of fraudulent use of identity can be properly investigated in the future.To manage returns of products or possible claims of faulty products or services, we need to collect and process your personal information. In order to prevent fraud in connection with claims and returns, we may need to request certain personal information from you to handle your request.To carry out marketing activities and optimise the customer browsing experience we use a number of methods in our marketing when collecting your personal data. For instance:We may use the information we collect from you to analyse how you shop and what you shop for. This allows us in the future to provide a browsing experience which is relevant to you and ensures that we provide you with marketing materials which are relevant to your needs and tastes;To show you products and services during your browse time which appear relevant from the information we have about you. This can include using the data you provide for statistical purposes and analysing how we can improve the services, products or website for you;To allow you to set up a personal profile on our website; so that you can set up an PMSA account. If you choose, you can also use your account to subscribe to e-mail newsletters from us. So that you can shop online with us. This enables you to purchase PMSA products and services online without having to fill in your personal information every time you shop online with us. To contact you about the experience you have had whilst in Looe or at an PMSA event so that we can find out about what we are doing well and what we can improve on;To respond to any experiences you had when shopping with us. For instance, you may have asked us questions on our social networking sites and we may reply to you;To improve the PMSA website and to ensure that the content is secure, presented in the best manner for you and your computer or mobile deviceWhere is your personal information stored?We keep the personal information we collect about you in secure environments. Your personal information is protected from unauthorised access, disclosure, use, alteration or destruction by any organisation or individuals. Some countries outside of the European Economic Area have laws and policies that do not guarantee the same protections as within the European Economic Area. Where your personal information is transferred outside of the European Economic Area we make sure that your personal information is protected in the same way as if it were here and we take all reasonably necessary steps to ensure that the data is kept private and held securely.Do you link to other websites? Our website may contain links to and from third party websites. These websites have their own privacy policies. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please make sure that you read their privacy policies before you submit any information to these websites. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies.No longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes? If you do not wish to be contacted about our products or services, you can unsubscribe via any newsletter (simply follow the unsubscribe link provided in marketing emails you receive from us) or by writing to us at: PMSA, 70 Cowcross Street, London, EC1M 6EJ.Need to update your records? If you find that the personal information we have about you is inaccurate or needs updating (for instance, you may have changed your name, address etc.) then please contact us so that we can correct it. PMSA is under a legal obligation to ensure that all the information we have about our customers is factually correct and kept up to date. To do this, please write to us at: PMSA, 70 Cowcross Street, London, EC1M 6EJ.Access to your information If you want to know what information PMSA holds about you, we will provide you with that information free of charge within 40 days of receiving the request. To obtain this information, please write to us at: 70 Cowcross Street, London, EC1M 6EJ.
Public Monuments and Sculpture Association
70 Cowcross Street,
London, England, EC1M 6EJ,
United Kingdom
Hours
Subscribe to our NewsletterSign up to our quarterly newsletter to receive information about PMSA events, awards, projects and exciting developments in the world of sculpture and public monuments.
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
Subscribe
Thank you!
About
PMSA Vision
PMSA Team
Contact
Privacy Policy
Impact
National Recording Project
Sculpture Awards
Sculpture Journal
News
© 2019 PUBLIC MONUMENTS AND SCULPTURE ASSOCIATION70 Cowcross Street | London | EC1M 6EJ | United KingdomRegistered charity number 1064519 Cover photo credit: Richard Youell. SCALLOP by Maggi Hambling © The copyright holder.
